WWW: Online Digital Resume

JACK GRIFFIN

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Talented emerging Front-end engineer, I can help end users with issues, I will read, write, and debug code for you, I will look into the exact reasoning your message did not arrive with the recipient. I will help with all this and more with my ever expanding toolbox. If I don't know it I will research it and solve it still. I love problems and I will happily resolve the most confusion programming issues I can daily.

SKILLS

- TECHNICAL SKILLS
- Web:
- HTML5
- Programming: PHP
- Operating Systems: Windows,
- MacOS, Linux
- Network and Information
- Virtualization: VMWare, Microsoft Hyper-V, Oracle VM
- Research: Source Checking

- Networking
- Advanced Google Search
- Email: Filters, Folders, Rules,
- Encryption
- Google Drive: Docs, Sheets,
- Debugging
- Logic
- Telecommunications
- Computer Hardware

- Active Directory
- Servers
- PowerShell
- Backup & Recovery
- Server Administration
- Group Policy
- DNS (Domain Name Service)
- DHCP

WORK HISTORY

CERTIFIED TECHNICAL ADVISOR 05/2022 to Current The IT Support Center

- Served as primary point of contact for triaging technical issues.
- Windows and Linux Server

TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST 08/2021 to 07/2022 ZixCorp

- Encryption/Archiving/Backup Support
- Assisted customers in identifying issues and explained solutions to restore service and functionality.
- Explained technical information in clear terms to non-technical individuals to promote better understanding.
- Monitored systems in operation and input commands to troubleshoot areas.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE 11/2021 to 03/2022 Liberty Tax

- Assisted customers in identifying issues and explained solutions to restore service and functionality.
- Resolved diverse range of technical issues across multiple systems and applications for customers and end-users across various time zones.
- Collaborated with supervisors to escalate and address customer inquiries or technical

issues.

Translated complex technical issues into digestible language for non-technical users.

SERVER ADMINISTRATOR 05/2021 to 08/2021 IMSUCCESSBLUEPRINT.COM

- Installed, configured, and supported local area network (LAN), wide area network (WAN) and Internet system.
- Maintained network hardware and software and monitored network to support network availability to end users.
- Performed day-to-day LAN and WAN administration, maintenance and support.
- Constructed and maintained Virtual Local Area Network (VLAN).

TECH SUPPORT 11/2020 to 05/2021 Liberty Tax

- Troubleshot and diagnosed problems to accurately resolve wide range of technical issues.
- Explained technical information in clear terms to non-technical individuals to promote better understanding.
- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Responded to support requests from end users and patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.

DELIVERY DRIVER, ASSISTANT MANAGER, GENERAL MANAGER 01/2014 to 01/2020 Domino's Pizza

- Trained, supervised, and evaluated staff, enabling them to improve skills and achieve daily objectives
- Provided excellent Customer Service ensuring repeat business
- Handled cost control, inventory control, cash control, and customer relations
- Demonstrated excellent time management and achieved company goals

EDUCATION

MyComputerCareer, Arlington, TX

Information Technology Security Administrator, Information Technology, 09/2020 CompTIA Certifications Earned: CompTIA A+ | Comptia NETWORK+ | Comptia Server+ | Comptia Security+ | Comptia Secure Infrastructure Specialist | Comptia Network Infrastructure Professional | Comptia Operations Specialist

MTA Certifications Earned: MTA Server Fundamentals | MTA Security Fundamentals | MTA Networking Fundamentals

CERTIFICATIONS

- CompTIA A+
- Comptia NETWORK+
- Comptia Server+
- Comptia Security+
- Comptia Secure Infrastructure Specialist
- Comptia Network Infrastructure Professional
- Comptia Operations Specialist
- MTA Server Fundamentals

- MTA Security Fundamentals
- MTA Networking Fundamentals